testing Ai generate subs, please disable if uncomfortable. warning is removed at 0:15
Hi.
The comments are so funny
saying congratulations
on winning three crowns.
Thanks.
The comments
are really fast.
Did everyone come in to congratulate us?
Am I not tired?
I'm not tired.
You want to know
ah
how to make
Maru
answer
you?
You just stroke him like this
and when you talk to him
he answers.
Maru do you like mom?
How much? A lot?
You like me a lot.
Thanks.
Like this
you just stroke him
and when you stop he answers.
Maru agung-ppang.
You want me to do it?
Maru
Maru agung-ppang
let's do it come here.
Come here. Agung-ppang.
Agung-ppang.
Maru agung-ppang.
You hate it?
Agung-ppang.
You hate it.
Then get down.
Maru.
Maru-ppang.
So cute.
Ah
by the way
did you notice
how much I cherish Maru?
How did I fix my hat in place?
So
at M Countdown
for the marine look outfit
I wore a hat.
Because it was pretty
really.
Ah
right
marine
look.
Oh maybe that wasn't it.
Anyway
when
back then
you put a safety pin
on the hat.
And then
you use a bobby pin
to secure the safety pin to your hair
like this.
That day
I think I used
really around
bobby pins.
Hmm it didn't
hurt though.
You just
put the hat on
fix it with bobby pins and then
turn your head like this.
Like this
shake it hard.
Then
even if you
shake your head
if it doesn't fall off
you just go up on stage like that.
The hair stylist
put in that much effort.
You want to know behind-the-scenes stories from the relay dance too?
Ah so
uh
I made a mistake I'm sorry.
It was so funny.
This wasn't the right rhythm.
Ah well
it was actually better.
It was funny.
Originally
I was supposed to do this and hand it over like this
but I
did this twice.
Where did the
chocolate tip
go?
Did you eat this?
So scary.
Who ate it?
Maru
did Maru eat it?
Oh Maru ate it.
Was it good?
Maru.
Huh?
He's
giving me
a massage
right now.
Ah why do I want to laugh?
Ah this
Mom is putting this in right?
Then
this will spread as a Shorts video
and create a controversy
that's a big deal.
So
do you know this?
Hmm.
Before
turning on the live
I thought about using a filter
but I
looked too
washed out.
So I held back today.
Is it okay if I use a filter?
Thanks.
I'll put the filter on
and do it confidently.
There
Hello.
Ah
I was going to give it to Flover
but I ate it.
I'll give it to you
next time.
Maru
can you
make that for me?
Done.
If I go bang
Maru pops up
right?
Okay here I go.
Do you know what this is?
First of all
again ah the vibe was different
it was about this much
again
once more
okay
next
With this much
can I pet him?
If I just do this
Maru Maru
Maru Maru.
With this much
I can give you
two connected
ones.
I'll go with the last one.
One
two three
Maru Maru
Maru mom is
working right now
Maru
okay
you
get an agung-ppang.
Here
agung-ppang
What's this? You're doing it today?
Let's do it together.
This is enough right?
A little
Maru
hey
Ah you want to know
the lyric interpretation
for Screen Time?
Ah but
the lyric interpretation for Screen Time is on this phone
right now.
Ah I didn't think of that.
I promised to explain
the lyrics for Screen Time.
I was a fool.
I kept revising the lyrics for Screen Time
a few times.
I kept revising it
so
I'll
explain it properly
next time.
Cheek-ppang
Cheek-ppang is this.
Huh?
What did you say?
You're asking if doing it on the chin
is a chin-ppang?
No this is
agung-ppang.
And this is
cheek-ppang.
Flover
how was this promotion?
It was good.
I really
liked it too.
Time flew by so fast.
Good times
always seem to pass by quickly.
Come
right here.
Up until the third crown
I had fun.
Oh come to think of it
time really does
feel like it's passing
so fast all of a sudden.
We are at 50 on Melon.
Flover must be listening to it a lot.
Today has a bit of
a
calm
vibe.
And
it's Monday tomorrow.
Since it's Monday
I hope you
can sleep well
and get some rest.
If we do
a concert
will a lot of Flovers
come?
Are there any Flovers watching
right now who are coming to the concert?
You're really coming right?
If you don't come
I'll just have fun
without you.
I'd love it
if you came
even just
for one day.
Even if I use a lint roller
on my clothes to remove the cat hair
it's exactly
the same.
It just keeps getting covered again and again.
I guess there's nothing you can do about it if you have a cat.
So cute.
You want me to wear it again?
No way.
Wow
that candy expression
it's been a really long time.
I don't even remember which eye
or which side the tongue is on.
It's been so long
but it was kind of like this.
You're asking how long I'll be doing the live today?
Uh
honestly I planned to do it
until 11:30
but I kinda want to do a little more.
Just 5 more minutes.
Flover you have to sleep for tomorrow.
Tomorrow is Monday.
That's why you have to go quickly.
I should also
go to sleep early for tomorrow.
You're just leaving it to tomorrow's you?
You're on vacation.
Then
that changes things a bit.
I guess you could
hang out a bit more.
Office worker Flovers
don't have vacations.
Student Flovers
need to know this fact.
Office worker
Flovers
don't have such a thing
as vacation.
Monday
is just Monday.
So
if you sleep past
12 AM
your morning
will be a little tiring.
But
office worker Flovers
fighting
and student Flovers
enjoy your
vacation well
you'll all experience
the Monday blues
of an office worker
eventually.
Maru is really long right?
Maru
really long right? Maru
has pretty paws.
Come out.
Ah during the video call
fan sign today
I saw a female Flover
who had
really pretty hands.
Her hands were so pretty.
That's what
I thought.
A pose I'm
obsessed with lately?
Yeah
no lately it's this
this one this one
Beok-ppeok?
Beok-ppeok.
I think this is
a bit cute.
Since it's cute I've been
pushing it a lot
rather than pushing it I just
use it a lot these days.
Doesn't the word
beok-ppeok sound so cute?
When I first
heard the word
beok-ppeok
I thought it meant to receive a lot of luck.
Like
getting luck three times
or receiving lots of luck
I thought it was something like that but it turns out
it's actually
like scratching
roughly
like that.
Beok-ppeok beok-ppeok
like this
right?
So I guess it means
I just interpreted it
like giving you
luck
that strongly.
Yeah it means something like that.
Anyway that's just my own interpretation.
The comments are saying
If you disagree
you're right.
Is that right?
If you disagree
you're right.
5 minutes have passed.
I should go.
I really have to go.
I'm really going.
What did you say?
Encore.
Ah suddenly
right before I go
the sound of an encore
is really nice.
Listening to one more song.
Are you asking if there's an encore for this concert?
Who knows.
There might not be an encore.
Do they usually do encores at concerts?
I'm not sure.
Do they usually?
I really don't know.
Encore.
Hmm
what is
an encore?
I have no idea.
You'll have to come
and find out
for yourself.
Come and see.
Flover.
Ah I kept petting Maru
so his fur
kept getting on me.
I have a really
great item.
Usually
you gather
the fur
but if you keep using
lint rollers
it ends up
costing a lot of money.
If you just do it
like this
you can see it
right?
And then you just
put it together
and throw it away.
But it takes a lot of strength.
So
I don't recommend
using it when you don't have
much energy.
If you need
a workout
it's good to use then.
For those who have cats
it's like this.
There's really a lot of fur.
Cat
with a cat
it can't be helped.
Just gotta accept it.
But
actually
even if I work hard
to remove it
it'll just get on me again.
So
honestly
they aren't allowed in my room
at home.
So
if I go into the room
I use the lint roller first
and hang my clothes up.
But when cats
go into a room
they're
not allowed in
they like it
so much.
Their tails
vibrate and everything.
Date me?
Wait a second.
Ah
I try not to read comments like this but I keep
reading them without realizing.
Right
it's time to date now.
You've liked me for a long time.
It's time to date.
Right? Maru.
Wow why did the comment speed get so fast?
Ah but
ah
just
uh
dating for 5 seconds
you know that kind of thing.
I think that would be better.
Like this.
Hmm.
I can't even speak.
After 5 seconds
everyone is
my
ex now.
Let's pretend it never happened.
The dating thing.
Where are you?
What are you doing?
Where are you and what are you doing?
Who are you with?
Who is it?
This is driving me crazy.
Why aren't you replying fast?
Ah what are you doing?
Ah I'm so anxious right now.
Anxious.
So anxious.
Anxious attachment
type vibes.
What does secure attachment
feel like?
Ah
yesterday
uh
what could it be? Hmm
hmm.
Ah yesterday
you couldn't contact me because
you were hanging out with friends.
That makes sense.
Good job.
Hmm okay.
I'll
Vibes like this. Secure attachment.
Ah so it's this kind of vibe.
Ah no it's not this kind of vibe.
This is even scarier.
Hmm.
That's anxious
anxious.
I'm not getting a reply
and you're not picking up the phone.
I'd contact their friend.
I can't reach them.
I don't know where they are or what they're doing.
And the friend
says it's fine.
Just
wait a little bit.
Hold on.
What do I do
if it's like this?
Just
this kind of anxiety.
Ah I think the anxious type would be a bit hard.
The anxious type
would be
a bit
exhausting right.
Flirting.
What flirting methods
are there?
As for flirting
methods
actually
I always feel this but
when I look at someone and think
wow I really like this person
this person is a really good person
there are times I feel like this.
And then
it was always someone who speaks beautifully.
Uh
speaking beautifully
is
a bit of
an ambiguous
standard
though.
Usually what I felt
was that a person who speaks
positively
felt to me like
they speak
beautifully.
Hmm.
Like
for example
really
simple
things.
Like saying
let's eat ice cream.
But the other person
didn't want to eat ice cream.
Even so
they say yes let's eat it.
Replying like this.
Ah
this analogy is a bit weird but
anyway
when the other person
agrees well
with what you suggest
They might have
their own opinions
too but
accommodating
as much as possible
I feel like wow
they're really accommodating.
That's how it felt.
Whenever Flover
suggests something
I'm usually
very
accommodating right?
I mean
you know I
as I've
lived hmm
oh I heard this at the fan sign today.
Early in my debut
I had
a bit of a sharp
side to me
but these days I've
become
much softer.
I heard that a lot.
Come to
think of it
it's not that
my sharp
sides
all became
perfectly rounded.
I don't think they're all rounded
I'm just not showing my sharp sides to Flovers anymore.
Of course
I still have sharp edges
and definitely have
sensitive parts too.
I'm just trying my best
to show
only the good sides to Flovers.
Because
now that it's my 9th
year
ah
doing this makes them dislike it
and ah doing this makes them like it.
Realizing this
uh
I focus on
what they like
and cater to it
which is why
in a way
my perceived personality
seems to have
changed
like this.
Of course
even if I show my sharp
sides
Flovers will still
like me.
There are definitely Flovers
who will like me regardless but
still
I think it's just that.
You guys like
this side of me
so I keep
trying to
show the side
you like.
This is also me
and the
sensitive me is also me.
There are
obviously times when I'm sensitive
and that's also me.
A person
can't always
be smiling right?
It's kind of like that.
Hmm.
I'm
an INFP you know.
But I
mentioned before
that my MBTI
changed.
I didn't even know.
I thought I would live
my whole life
as an INFP
but I got a pretty shocking
MBTI
result.
I took
the paid version
and it changed so much
I tried so hard not to change
so
it changing so much
completely surprised me.
So
I thought to myself
ah let's find my INFP
again.
Let's become
warmer.
I really thought about that a lot.
So
I tried to
become much warmer.
Because
honestly hmm
there are a lot of people
whose MBTI
has changed.
But the reason I don't reveal my changed MBTI
is uh
just
to Flovers hmm
it's cute right.
I want to remain
as a cute person.
And in front of Flovers
I want to hold on to more romance
and be
moved more
and live
more optimistically.
I think that's it.
It's almost 12
already.
Let's just do it
until 12 for now.
Originally
ah time goes by so fast.
Did I turn this on at 11?
Then
since you have to overcome
the Monday blues
once it hits
exactly
Monday at 12
I will
get going.
Really
thanks again
for the 1st place
this time.
Thank you
so much.
When we got 1st place on a music show
for the first time
it
felt
unbelievable.
And then
after getting 1st place
uh
I thought that
we are people
who can
win 1st place.
Thinking that
when we
came back this time
I definitely didn't
take that 1st place
for granted.
Our company
yeah.
Uh
I think they put in a lot of effort.
Because they worked hard
to get us good broadcast points
working so hard
there was that kind of effort
and Flovers' effort too.
That's why
I think it happened.
The result of everyone's efforts
combined.
You guys
worked
really hard.
Honestly
right after promotions
ended today
I really wanted
to eat Yeoptteok.
Yeah.
Promotions are over
but there are still charts
so
today
I'm finishing the day with a World Cone.
And it's better to eat it tomorrow
since it's too late today.
You guys too
if possible
don't eat late-night snacks
too late at night.
You'll
get esophagitis.
Reflux
esophagitis.
Now 1 minute left.
Now
at 12
I'm going to go.
Like this
Sunday
night.
And
Monday.
Monday
night.
Uh the start of
Monday.
Did you have fun watching
the live we spent together
for these two days?
Oh
you had fun watching it with Maru.
Maru
not fun
No I mean Flover.
I almost said
Maru instead.
To Flover
Flover
you worked so hard
today.
It was so much fun
and I was happy.
Thank you so much for running with us
through this promotion
and even though
our promotions
are over hmm
our song
is still ranking
right now and
uh honestly that's it
what is it
in the meantime
you listened to it more
Go get some rest
thank you.
Shall we do a capture time for the last part?
Capture time.
Did you work hard?
What should I do?
Nice right.
Have sweet dreams.
Always
thankful.
Which exit today?
Today
we won 3 crowns so
let's go to exit 3.
It's exit 3.
Come to the exit.
Let's properly celebrate
the 3 crowns.
Got it?
I will get going now.
I
had so much fun
today
thank you for spending
the end of my day with me like this.
I'm going to go now.
I should just say bye.
Hmm.
I'm going to go.
Now I have to undo my hair
and everything.
I cherish you
a lot
and I like you
a whole lot.
Good night which exit today?
Which exit today?
Right exit 3.
Why exit 3?
It's to
celebrate
our 3 crowns
that's why we're gathering at exit 3 Flover.
Bye.
Oh this looks like a selfie.
Hurry hurry
I'm really
bye